- (indistinct) If you didn't
come to the throw down
in the A Town, I guess I see you round,
but right now I'm gonna
get into the number one
most requested record from the Ghost Town.
Right now, it's called "My Boo!"
♪ Boy, you should know that ♪
♪ I've got you on my mind ♪
♪ Your secret admirer ♪
♪ I've been watching you ♪
♪ At night, I think of you ♪
♪ I want to be your lady, maybe ♪
♪ If your game is on, give me a call boo ♪
♪ If your lovin's strong,
gonna give my all to you ♪
♪ At night, I think of you ♪
♪ I want to be your lady, maybe ♪
♪ If your game is on, give me a call boo ♪
♪ If your lovin's strong,
gonna give my all to you ♪
♪ Every day I pray my heart can win ♪
♪ Every night I pray I
can call you my man ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I need you, I want you ♪
♪ To have you, hold you, squeeze you ♪
♪ So I'm going out, every weekend ♪
♪ Just to see my boo again ♪
♪ At night, I think of you ♪
♪ I want to be your lady, maybe ♪
♪ If your game is on, give me a call boo ♪
♪ If your lovin's strong,
gonna give my all to you ♪
♪ At night, I think of you ♪
♪ I want to be your lady, maybe ♪
♪ If your game is on, give me a call boo ♪
♪ If your lovin's strong,
gonna give my all to you ♪
♪ These feelings I have for you ♪
♪ Can go deeper if you can come ♪
♪ Correct with your game boy (no, no) ♪
♪ No you can't be lame boy ♪
♪ But if you can please me ♪
♪ Then my love will come easy ♪
♪ I'll do anything you want ♪
♪ Freak me boy, I'm thinking of you ♪
♪ At night, I think of you ♪
♪ I want to be your lady, maybe ♪
♪ If your game is on, give me a call boo ♪
♪ If your lovin's strong,
gonna give my all to you ♪
♪ At night, I think of you ♪
♪ I want to be your lady, maybe ♪
♪ If your game is on, give me a call boo ♪
♪ If your lovin's strong,
gonna give my all to you ♪
♪ Boy you've got all I need ♪
♪ From what I see ♪
♪ And boy ♪